instrumentpro.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy - Instrument Pro

|  |   
---  
|   
Guitars:  
---  
Electric Guitar  
Acoustic Guitar  
Guitar Packages  
Other Stringed  
Guitar Amplifiers  
Guitar Effects  
Guitar Wireless Systems  
Guitar Accessories  
Guitar Books & Videos  
Bass Guitars:  
Electric Bass  
Acoustic Bass  
Bass Packages  
Bass Amplifiers  
Bass Effects  
Bass Wireless Systems  
Bass Accessories  
Bass Books & Videos  
Drums:  
Acoustic Drums  
Electronic Drums  
World/Latin Percussion  
Drum Machines  
Hardware  
Snare Drums  
Cymbals  
Accessories  
Keyboards:  
Keyboard Synthesizers  
Digital Pianos  
Keyboard Amplifiers  
Keyboard Controllers  
Keyboard Modules & Samplers  
Software & Plug-Ins  
Theremins  
Keyboard Cases & Stands  
Keyboard Accessories  
Recording:  
Multitrack Recorder  
Computer Hardware  
Recording Microphones  
Recording Computer Software  
Recording Mixers  
Studio Monitors  
Recording Headphones  
Recording Signal Processors  
Recording Accessories  
Live Sound:  
Live Sound Mixers  
PA Speakers  
Power Amplifiers  
Live Sound Microphones  
Wireless Microphones  
Signal Processing  
Karaoke  
Live Sound Cases & Stands  
Live Sound Accessories  
DJ Gear:  
Turntables  
CD Players  
DJ Mixers  
DJ Systems  
DJ Microphones  
DJ Headphones  
DJ Cartridges  
DJ Speakers  
DJ Power Amplifiers  
Groove Machines  
DJ Cases & Stands  
DJ Accessories  
Lighting Equipment:  
Effects Lighting  
Stage Lighting  
Laser Lighting  
Special Effects  
Fog, Snow, & Bubble Machines  
Lighting Accessories  
Band Instruments:  
Brass  
Woodwind  
Stringed Instruments  
Accessories  
Manufacturers  
  
| 

Effective November 5th, 2004 

### Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

  * ### Our Commitment To Privacy

    * Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 
  * ### The Information We Collect

    * This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the instrumentpro.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 
      * Name 
      * Address 
      * Email address 
      * Phone number 
      * Credit/Debit Card Information 
    * On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 
      * Name 
      * Address 
      * Phone Number 
  * ### The Way We Use Information

    * We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 
    * We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 
    * We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 
    * You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. 
    * We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 
    * Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. 
  * ### Our Commitment To Data Security

    * To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 
  * ### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

    * Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 
  * ### How You Can Correct Your Information

    * You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending a request to [Customer Service](mailto:customerservice@instrumentpro.com) that credibly shows error. 
    * To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 
  * ### How To Contact Us

    * Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800.805.0852 or send us an email at [Customer Service](mailto:customerservice@instrumentpro.com). 

**Warning** : MagpieRSS: Failed to fetch http://www.instrumentpro.com/blog/wp-feed.php?category_name=Privacy&feed=rss (HTTP Response: HTTP/1.1 403 Forbidden ) in **/home/sites/site236/html/include/magpierss/rss_fetch.inc** on line **238**  

|
